http://www.bookrags.com/about/terms.htm

Terms of Service
BookRags is an information- and service-oriented web site. The use of the free and paid services is at your own risk. BookRags does not guarantee that service will continue uninterrupted. Any materials viewed, read, or downloaded from BookRags.com is also at your own risk. Although we make every effort to provide accurate, error-free content, BookRags gives no guarantee of any kind that its materials are written with accurate content, descriptions, or opinions. In addition, BookRags gives no guarantee or assurance that its work is error free. BookRags does not offer any guarantees that the materials that are downloaded will be virus free. By using the BookRags.com web site in any manner you understand and agree with these policies.
Registration
By submitting the user registration form, you are affirming that the information provided is accurate as of the date entered. Furthermore, you will make all necessary attempts to change your registration information if it should change for any reason.
BookRags shall have the right (but not the obligation) in its sole discretion to refuse or move any Content that is available via the Service.
Email and Personal Information Privacy
Please view our Privacy Policy for information on your email and other personal information. If you are a parent of a child and have a particular concern, please contact BookRags through the Customer Service Department.
Plagiarism
When utilizing the BookRags resources in any work including essay, book, poem, or any other form of written literature, you must give BookRags.com as your source and have it appropriately cited and documented. BookRags.com will not be held responsible for plagiarism of the BookRags site of any kind. By using the BookRags services and information, you are held accountable for any attempts to copy, maneuver, or alter the BookRags text for your own use. Using, reading, or downloading the BookRags.com materials in any way is at your own discretion and risk. You are solely accountable for your usage of the site materials.
For more on plagiarism, visit: Plagiarism/HowtoCiteonBookRags
Language and Conduct
You will be held solely responsible for any language used on the BookRags Q&A/Homework Help. BookRags is not responsible for any conduct derived from the BookRags site including the Q&A/Homework Help. Reading the Q&A/Homework Help is solely at your own risk. The interpretations of other posting made on the Q&A/Homework Help are entirely at your own risk. You are solely responsible for your conduct, as it is applicable to your local, state, national, and international laws and regulations. BookRags is not responsible for harassing, offensive, violent, lewd, discriminatory, promotional, illegal, threatening, or libelous postings on its Q&A/Homework Help. Furthermore, BookRags reserves the right to terminate any user from accessing the web site for any actions that are deemed or even suspected, in BookRags opinion, unreasonable or that fall into the preceding list. Neither BookRags nor any of its partners or affiliates will be held responsible for any breach of the warranty. By using the BookRags Q&A/Homework Help, you grant BookRags the exclusive rights to translate, alter, modify, update, delete, or make any other edits which are desired by BookRags.
Password Protection
BookRags is not responsible for the misuse of your user password. If you believe that someone else has misused your password, you must let BookRags know immediately. BookRags cannot be held liable for the misuse of your password. To change your password, login and click on “My Account” in the upper, right-hand corner. Then click on “Account Information”, enter a new password, then click “Save”.
Disclaimer
The information in BookRags is published for the sole purpose of intellectual stimulation, education and general knowledge. The materials on BookRags have been made using extensive and detailed research. However, despite BookRags’ best efforts, the content may not be accurate or complete. None of the book notes, study guides, lesson plans, or any of the content on BookRags should replace reading the book itself. All of the content should be seen as guides to help users learn more about a particular subject and expand their knowledge. The purpose of all of the content on BookRags is to provide fun and useful tools to users to promote general education and understanding. BookRags makes no warranty to the accuracy, completeness, usefulness, value, or fairness of the content, nor does BookRags guarantee against errors, failed links, omissions, or lost data on the site. BookRags makes no guarantee that tests cover all data, information, resources, etc.
User Profiles
Individual profiles can be modified, deleted, or altered in any way that BookRags deems reasonable.
Credit Cards
Misuse of credit cards through theft or other illegal measure will not be permitted on BookRags. Those who use illegal/stolen credit cards on BookRags will be punished to the full extent of the law and those actions will be considered a breach of the Terms of Service.
Material Ownership
All of the Content on BookRags.com is copyrighted. BookRags content may be downloaded or printed for personal use, but may not be distributed for any reason whatsoever. Any distribution of BookRags content is a violation of the copyrighted works. Any individual, company, or entity found to have copied from BookRags will be punished to the fullest extent of the law. No copies, sales, modifications, uploading, or any other form of copyright infringement is permitted.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold BookRags and its agents, affiliates, officers, or employees, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of Content you submit, post, transmit or make available through BookRags, your use of BookRags, your connection to BookRags, your violation of the TOS, or your violation of any rights of another.
Guidelines Regarding Children
Our products and services are marketed for and directed towards purchase by adults or with the consent of adults. By accepting these Terms of Service through your use of the Site, you certify that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms of Service. BookRags.com does not knowingly collect personal information about children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. Should we learn that someone under the age of 13 has provided any personal information to BookRags.com we will remove that information as soon as possible. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site other than for browsing, and parents or legal guardians may not agree to these Terms of Service on their behalf. If you are a parent or legal guardian agreeing to these Terms of Service for the benefit of a child between the ages of 13 and 18, be advised that you are fully responsible for his or her use of this Site, including all financial charges and legal liability that he or she may incur.
Subscriptions and Cancellations
BookRags offers a variety of products sold as ongoing monthly or annual subscriptions. When a purchase is made, the buyer is sent a confirmation email with a precise record of their purchase. Please make sure that your purchase is correct at the time of your order by verifying it before you make your purchase.
Monthly subscriptions may be cancelled at any time by logging into your account and clicking on the "My Account" link in the upper right, then clicking the "Manage Subscription" button. There will then be a gray 'Cancel' button next to any active subscription.  Press that button to cancel the subscription.  Once a subscription billing date has passed, you cannot obtain a refund for that month's charge. If you have any questions, please contact us.
In addition, once you make a purchase with us, there is no way in which the study guide can be returned since it can be downloaded, viewed, and printed immediately following your payment. In effect, the study guide is immediately consumed once the purchase is made because there is no way we can get the study guide back or have a user return it. Unless there is an error on the website, you are responsible for the purchase. This is true even if you email us right away.
Please note that we do provide a lot of information up front so that you can make an informed purchase decision when buying from BookRags. Prior to any purchase, we include:
A sample study guide and lesson plan
The length of the study guide, lesson plan, essay, literary criticism, biography, etc.
The beginning of each product or each section of each product (if applicable) for free
All of the section titles on the left-hand navigation bar for study guide and lesson plans so that you can see which sections are included
All of the study pack products (with a preview for each) on the study pack page
"As Is" Warranty
Content on the website is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. BookRags makes no warranty whatsoever as to the accuracy or completeness of the Content or the results to be obtained from using the information contained on the website. Neither BookRags nor any of its data suppliers will be responsible for any claims attributable to errors, omissions, or other inaccuracies in the information contained in the Content. The entire risk for the results and performance of the Content is assumed by the User. Further, BookRags makes no representations or warranties, either express or implied, with respect to the Content, including, but not limited to, the quality, performance, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose of the Content or any information contained therein. In no event will BookRags be liable for direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of the use of or inability to use the Content or for any loss or damage of any nature caused to any person as a result of that use.
Additional Information
The Terms of Service is an agreement between you the user and BookRags. The Terms of Service and the agreement between you and BookRags shall follow the laws governed by the State of Delaware.
If you feel that someone has violated our Terms of Service, please contact BookRags via customer service, or at the following address:
BookRags, Inc.
999 3rd Ave.
Suite 700
Seattle, WA 98104
Related articles
Privacy Policy
How do I cancel my subscription?
About BookRags
Contact BookRags.com
How much is a subscription to BookRags?
Article is closed for comments.
Powered by Zendesk
